That's another example about bubbles saw before moving to implementing the bubbles sort algorithm in
language.
And the next video, we are going to create an example exercise about bubble sort in Java.
So Bubbles sort is one algorithm used to sort a sequence of numbers.
Consider we have nine numbers here from one to nine.
We are having them in unordered sequence.
The scale at the right and of the sequence will compare that to numbers on their left and right sides.
OK.
So in this case, it will start comparing from seven and six.
This is the same way for you, whether you start the scale from the right or the left.
We need to get a sorted way sorted algorithm, the components using this mobile sort algorithm.
So in this case, we will compare seven and six after comparing comparing them.
If the number on the right is found to be smaller, the numbers will be swapped.
In this case, we are going to swap that.
After that, it moves to the next to the next two numbers, so after the comparison is finished, the
scale moves one position to the left.
The numbers are compared once again and this time six is greater than four.
So the numbers don't get swept.
The scale move, one position to the left.
This operation is repeated until the scales reach the left and of their seat, so it will compare eight
with four.
Eight is greater than four, so it would be swept to is less than four.
It will not change one less than two.
Not changed.
Three is greater than one.
So we swapped them.
One is being.
Being greater than nine in this case, so it is not correct, so one is less than nine.
And five is great and is greater than one.
Yes.
So we need to sweep it, OK, until reaching the end of the sequence.
Once the scale have reached their left end of the sequence and the one round operation, the smallest
value in this sequence has moved to that left edge.
The number on the left edge is considered fully sorted.
OK, no.
And the scale the scales are moved back to the right edge again, six and seven being compared.
We move at eight and six being compared.
And so we swept them four and six, two and four, three and two.
We swept them nine and two, sweeping them five and two strapping them.
So one and two is considered as fully sorted.
Again, the same operation are repeated until that the all numbers of the fully sorted algorithms.
We start comparing them nine and three swap them three and five swap them one to three is being considered
as fully sorted.
Eight and seven seasons, four, nine and four swapping them.
Five and four.
We swap them again seven and six.
Six and nine.
So we swept them five and six.
Seven and eight, nine and seven, six and seven.
No.
Eight and nine.
We swept them seven and eight.
Seven is being considered as fully sorted, No.
Eight and nine is being sorted and nine have it, it becomes the greatest element.
So this operation will implement four, as will indicate for us, and concludes that the explanation
of bubble sawed air have been ended.
So this is the bubble sort.
This is how the algorithm behind the bubble sort of works.
Let's move to do sea language and see how it would be implemented, according to that to do that sea
compiler.